

CURICULUM VITAF IBRAHIM BELLO **FULL-STACK DEVELOPER**





ozzvcdes@gmail.com

+234 9026040774

226. Ifedano st. Owode Academy, Ibadan, Ovo State, Nigeria

www.ozzv-dev.netlifv.com

AROUT ME

I'm a skilled and passionate self-taught Full-Stack Developer from Nigeria, I have been fascinated with building a web application and solving problems using programming, my interest has led me to learn both font-end and backend technologies such as HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, ReactJs and NodeJs. I have taken part in many different projects, some of them personal, others, team project, I believe my experience with those projects makes me the best candidate for web development related work.

On my spare time, I love to play games, build projects and do freelance work.

HTML5 - CSS3 - SASS - JavaScript -

React, Js - Node, Js - Express - PostgrSql -

EDUCATION



IMAS | Science Depertment

2015 - 2018

IGCSEs in Science stream which included various subjects heavily foucusing on Biology, Chemistry, Physics, IT and other subjects too.

EXPERIENCE



Albarka Abode Computer Training | Front End Instructor 2019 - 2020

Taught web develoment technologies to trainee of age range 15 - 25 also Instruct and supervise their projects

Freelancer | Web Developer

2019 - Present

Design and develop proffesional website for bussineses and individuals using the technologies I've learned

CERTIFICATIONS



Codecademv:

Introduction to JavaScript

Udemv:

Prototype in AdobeXD Web Design for Web Developer The complete Web Developer in 2020 Complete React Developer in 2020

IELTS ACADEMIC BAND 6

SOFT SKILLS

MongoDB

TECHNOLOGIES



LANGUAGE



English - Yoruba



Music - Dancing - Football